Academy Award Winner Friz Freleng's Greatest Warner Bros. Comedy
Classics Plus All New Cartoons For the Big Screen.
The Looney, Looney, Looney Bugs Bunny Movie is a animation,
comedy, family film directed by Friz Freleng.
Bugs Bunny hosts an award show featuring several
classic Looney Tunes shorts and characters.
Bugs Bunny / King Arthur / Sir Osis of Liver / Sir Loin of Beef / Yosemite Sam / Gerry the Idgit Dragon / Daffy Duck / Sylvester / Tweety Pie / Porky Pig / Speedy
Gonzales / Treasury Director / Rocky / Mugsy / Judge / Clancy / O'Hara / Cops / Pepe Le Pew / Clarence (B.A. Bird) (voice), played by Mel Blanc.
Granny (voice), played by June Foray.
Granny (voice), played by Bea Benaderet.
The Singing Narrator / Big Bad Wolf / Three Little
Pigs (voice), played by Stan Freberg.
The Narrator (voice), played by Ralph James.
Satan (voice), played by Frank Nelson.
Witch Hazel is an animated cartoon character in the Warner Bros.
Looney Tunes and Merrie Melodies series of cartoons and TV shows.
Witch Hazel is a fairy tale witch antagonist with green skin, a round
figure, bulbous facial features, and a single tooth.
The name is a pun on the witch-hazel plant and folk remedies based on it.
Created by Chuck Jones during the golden age of American animation, the character
was originally voiced by Bea Benaderet in 1954's Bewitched Bunny.
Benaderet would later be replaced by June Foray, who voiced the character almost exclusively
beginning with 1956's Broom-Stick Bunny and concluding with 2002's Twick or Tweety.
Tress MacNeille would briefly voice Witch Hazel from 1992 to 1994
for episodes of Tiny Toon Adventures and Animaniacs.
After Foray's departure from the role, the character was voiced by Roz Ryan from 2011 to 2013
for The Looney Tunes Show (as Witch Lezah) and by Candi Milo from 2017 onward.
The film explores themes of cartoon, compilation, package film.
The tone is lighthearted.